Hello

I'm Chimezie Amazing

Owaza,asa ukwa West LGA Abia state ZIP CODE:512102 +(234) 07026872649 acelagendary2424@gmail.com

Skills

Meticulous Junior web developer with over 3+ months of front end experience and passion for responsive website design and a firm believer in the mobile-first approach.

Proficient in Git, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, HTTP, Responsive Design, Object Oriented Programming and Agile.

Experience

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

Start Innovation Hub, Uyo - *Software Engineering Intern*

- Learned how to build Website pages
- Learned to write Javascript Functions
- Collaborate with team in building To-Do, E-Commerce and Pharmaceutical web apps

March 2021 - June 2021

Zuri, **Virtual** - *Software Engineering Intern*

- Learned Basics of Software Engineering and Agile principles
- Learned how to write basic Javascript and DOM
- Learned to collaborate with teams and version control

Education

Sept. 2009- Aug. 2015

Sept. 2015 - Aug. 2021

Adventist Secondary Technical College, Owerrinta - W.A.S.S.C.E

Class of 2021, with a major in Applied science.

Awards

Awarded as best Innovative and Creative student for designing and implementing prototype Biogas systems with local materials .

SPONSORS, PHONE NUMBER AND ADDRESS

Mr and Mrs Chimezie John Ubani Phone.0803711131

ADDRESS: @ Owaza cottage hospital,asa ukwa West LGA abia state of Nigeria